WAER Collection
WAER Collection
1965-1979
WAER (Radio station: Syracuse, N.Y.)
18 linear ft.
Collection consists of non-commercial recordings, all off-air dubs on reel to reel tapes.
4526484
Biographical History
WAER is a radio station in Syracuse, NY, broadcasting at 88.3 MHz FM. Located on the campus of Syracuse University, it has been in operation since April 1, 1947. WAER was student-run until 1983, when operations were taken over by the university and the station became a member of National Public Radio (NPR). WAER currently serves the greater Syracuse area with NPR and local news, eclectic music, and Syracuse University sports. WAER is staffed by full-time professionals who train, educate, and supervise student volunteers interested in enhancing their experience in broadcast journalism and sports broadcasting. The station is best known for its sports programming, and the sports staff is made up entirely of students, broadcasting coverage of every football, men's basketball, and men's lacrosse game. WAER's sports staff has produced some of the biggest names in sports broadcasting, including Bob Costas, Marv Albert, Dick Stockton, and Mike Tirico.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The WAER collection consists of more than 250 reel to reel tapes. Few of the tapes are dated, but those that are cover a span from 1965 to 1979. Announcers or presenters are rarely identified. These tapes primarily hold topical broadcasts and live concert recordings. The news items include a mix of national and local productions, but there are relatively few in the collection compared to the concert recordings. Many concerts were given by popular artists such as Pink Floyd, Bonnie Raitt, Canned Heat, Niels Lofgren, and Commander Cody, taken from national broadcasts, mostly originating from New York City or Boston. The collection contains recordings of only a handful of concerts broadcast by Syracuse University student ensembles. 25 tapes are identified as having been recorded on-campus at the Jabberwocky Café; surviving performances from this intimate venue include those given by John Fahey, Taj Mahal, and David Bromberg.
Arrangement of the Collection
Items are arranged in order by ID number, but are listed in the inventory below in alphabetical order by title.
Subject and Genre Headings
Music; Radio, television, film; Syracuse University -- History.; WAER (Radio station: Syracuse, N.Y.); Radio broadcasting -- New York (State) -- Syracuse.; FM broadcasting -- New York (State) -- Syracuse.; Public radio -- New York (State) -- Syracuse.; Radio broadcasting of sports.; News radio stations -- New York (State) -- Syracuse.; Syracuse (N.Y.) -- History.; 78 rpm records.; Long-playing records.; Tape reels.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Researcher access to the recordings requires advance notice in order to produce a working copy.
Acquisition Information
Unknown.
Inventory
- Recordings
  Access to recordings requires advance notice to produce a use copy.
  - 1965 Year End Focus; Tolley Interview, waer_046; 1 reel tape (Oversize 4)
  - ABC Radio Network: Christmas Special, waer_023; includes fill music at the end; 1 reel tape (Oversize 2)
  - ABC Radio Network: Christmas Special, waer_025; 1 reel tape (Oversize 2)
  - ABC Radio Network: Christmas Special, Special Events Department WAER Radio, waer_024; 1 reel tape (Oversize 2)
  - Aired conspiracy segments, waer_152; 1 reel tape (Oversize 12)
  - All Go Our Own Way, waer_097; 1 reel tape (Oversize 8)
    I Once Loved a Girl; Sunset; Sausilito Bay Suite Break; Ballad of a Man; All Go Our Own Way
  - All University Council, waer_130; 1 reel tape (Oversize 10)
  - Art Ensemble of Chicago; Interview by Brian Auerbach, waer_195; 1 reel tape (Oversize 15)
  - At Poorhour 2-27-75, waer_172; 1 reel tape (Oversize 14)
  - Bat McGrath Jabberwocky 2/11/77, waer_081; 1 reel tape (Oversize 7)
  - Batsy Grand, waer_237; 1 reel tape (Oversize 17)
  - BC 1648.08 Power Trip: "Murray Bookchin N The Energy Crisis", waer_176; 1 reel tape (Oversize 14)
  - BC 1838b Audi(o)ting the Internal Revenue Servicing, waer_177; 1 reel tape (Oversize 14)
  - Beach Boys, waer_102; 1 reel tape (Oversize 8)
  - Ben Sidran (Interview), waer_221; 1 reel tape (Oversize 16)
  - Bengt Halberg / Gerry Mulligan, track one Bengt Halberg; track two Gerry Mulligan; waer_133; 1 reel tape (Oversize 11)
    Limehouse Blues; Pink Lady; Whiskey Sour; Side Car; Bill Not Phil; You’re Blase; D’Anjou; Imagination; Bijou; Poogerini; Gloomy Sunday; Black Strap; I Can’t Believe That You’re In Love With Me; Sextet;Lover Men; Lady Be Good; Carson City Stage; Cherry; Makin’ Whoopee; Motel; Meet Mr. Gordon; Two Can Play; What a Difference a Day Makes; Onion Bottom;Tea for Two; Modus Operandi; For Sue; Love is Here to Stay; Jeru; Moon Dreams; Venus de Milo; Deception; Godchild; Rocker; Israel; Roove; Liberty Bell; Have You Met Miss Jones; Isn’t It Romantic; Traditional
  - Best of Old Time Radio Oct 25, 1976 Immigrant, waer_247; 1 reel tape (Oversize 18)
  - Birth - live @ Studio C - 2/20/75, waer_074; 1 reel tape (Oversize 6)
  - Birth in Studio C, waer_076; 1 reel tape (Oversize 6)
  - Black Sheep Live, waer_113; 1 reel tape (Oversize 9)
    The Hunter; Cruisin; Work to be Done; Shapes of Things; Paying Yer Dues; Let Me Stay; Freight Train; Stick Around
  - Bluegrass ‘78, waer_127; 1 reel tape (Oversize 10)
    I Don’t Mean to Cry; I Just Got Wise; Wreck on the Highway; Windy Mountain; I’m Not Broke; When I Take My Vacation; Letters Have No Arms; Lorene; The Little Paper Boy; The Old Home Place; Pain In My Heart; Rambler’s Blues; Hello Stranger; The Great Atomic Power; ‘Til The End of the World; I Wonder How...; Chinquipire Pie; Midnight on the Water; Never See my Home Again; Way Out There
  - Bobby Hamilton, waer_158; 1 reel tape (Oversize 13)
  - Bonnie Raitt, waer_236; 1 reel tape (Oversize 17)
  - Box 6462 Stan Getz Radio Concert, waer_164; 1 reel tape (Oversize 13)
  - Boz Scaggs at Manley, waer_053; 1 reel tape (Oversize 5)
    1. Instrumental 2. I will forever sing the blues 3. We were always sweet hearts 4. Look what I’ve got
  - Brainwashing of American P.O.W.’s by Chinese Communists, waer_153; address to Eastman Kodak officers and supervisors; Major William E. Mayer, U.S. Army at Eastman Kodak in Rochester; includes questions from the audience after main address; 1 reel tape (Oversize 12)
  - Broadway and All That Jazz, waer_255; 1 reel tape (Oversize 18)
  - Canned Heat Interview by Louis Zellman: played with the turtles and spirit, waer_101; 1 reel tape (Oversize 8)
  - Carlene Carter Live at Jab 10/12/79 Tape 2, waer_184; 1 reel tape (Oversize 15)
  - Carlene Carter Live at Jab 10/12/79 Tape 7, waer_183; 1 reel tape (Oversize 15)
  - Carolyne Mas Live on WAER-Syracuse 9/7/79 Part 1, waer_185; 1 reel tape (Oversize 15)
  - Carolyne Mas Live on WAER-Syracuse 9/7/79 Part 2, waer_186; 1 reel tape (Oversize 15)
  - Cazenovia folk concert, part 1, waer_007; 1 reel tape (Oversize 1)
  - Cazenovia folk concert, part 2, waer_008; 1 reel tape (Oversize 1)
  - Cazenovia folk concert, part 3, waer_009; 1 reel tape (Oversize 1)
  - Chicago 7 Tape, waer_147; 1 reel tape (Oversize 12)
  - Chogyam Trungpa, Rinpoche, waer_244; 1 reel tape (Oversize 18)
  - Chris Williamson, waer_092; 1 reel tape (Oversize 8)
    1. Frontier; 2. Mr. Frank Jones; 3. Lovesick Blues; 4. Is It Really Love At All; 5. The Rising of the Sun; 6. Sweet Slow Slider; 7. Lean On Me; 8. Can I Believe My Eyes; 9. Joanna; 10. Flying on Home to You; 11. Indian Sunset
  - Citizen Corps politics; Max Lerner guest speaker, waer_131; 1 reel tape (Oversize 11)
  - City Boy Station I.D., waer_253; 1 reel tape (Oversize 18)
  - Cleve Backster, waer_246; 1 reel tape (Oversize 18)
  - Come Together, waer_118; 1 reel tape (Oversize 10)
  - Commander Cody Concert at Jab, waer_144; 1 reel tape (Oversize 12)
  - Commander Cody Concert: Part 1, waer_140; 1 reel tape (Oversize 11)
    Mama Tried; Lonely All the Time; Hot Rod Lincoln; First Look I look at the Purse; Lawdy Miss Clawdy; Gonna Hijack a Big Jet Plane; Diggy-Liggy Lie, Diggy Liggy Lo; Going Back to Birmingham; Little Sally Walker
  - Commander Cody Concert: Part 2, waer_142; 1 reel tape (Oversize 11)
    C-H-O-M-P Cheer; Riot Goin’ On in Cell Block Nine; Boppin’ the Blues; Be-Bop-A-Lula; Jailhouse Rock; Lost in the Ozone; Blue Suede Shoes.
  - Conspiracy Tapes Feb 15, 1970, waer_245; 1 reel tape (Oversize 18)
  - Corbally interview 2/1/71, waer_083; 1 reel tape (Oversize 7)
  - Country Granola, WAER Simulcast with Synapse Video, waer_122; 1 reel tape (Oversize 10)
    Mind Your Own Business; Dead-Eye Bill; Football Medley; Satin Doll/ Player’s Intro; Slide Mountain Row; I Gave Her the Ring; B Minor Song; Morning Light; Nothing’s Forever; New York City Water Supply; Blue Feeling; Dixie Breakdown; The Lucy Song; Lady Me Donalds; People May Laugh.
  - Country Granola: Part 1, waer_123; 1 reel tape (Oversize 10)
  - Country Granola: Part 2, waer_125; 1 reel tape (Oversize 10)
  - Cris Williamson - remote c’cant Jab, waer_105; 1 reel tape (Oversize 9)
  - Danny Douma Live at Jab, waer_217; 1 reel tape (Oversize 16)
  - David Amram, waer_219; 1 reel tape (Oversize 16)
  - David Bromberg and the Feb. Torpedoes, waer_156; 1 reel tape (Oversize 12)
  - David Bromberg at Jabberwocky, waer_093; 1 reel tape (Oversize 8)
    1. Six Days on the Road; 2. Good Mornin’ Little School Girl; 3. It Takes a Lot to Laugh, it Takes a Train to Cry; 4. Dig a Hole; 5. T for Texas; 6. The Jugband Song; 7. Wish Fiddle Tunes; 8. Blues; 9. Mr. Bojangles; 10. The Holdup; 11. Tryin to Get Home
  - David Bromberg on the Quad Sept. 10, 1976, waer_060; 1 reel tape (Oversize 5)
    1. Driving Wheel w/ Tom Rush 1A. UTZ I.D. 2. You Treat Your Daddy So Damn Mean 3. Will Not Be Yo’ Foo 4. Danger Man 5.
  - David Johansen, Jab tape 1, waer_218; 1 reel tape (Oversize 16)
  - Denny Hall, waer_240; 1 reel tape (Oversize 17)
  - Dick Sheridan Master, waer_167; 1 reel tape (Oversize 13)
  - Donald Byrd live at the Roxy Theater - Los Angeles., waer_161; 1 reel tape (Oversize 13)
  - Down City Ramblers, waer_226; tape reads "for radio spot; Thursday, January 31st at Jabberwocky The Down City Ramblers with Martha Trachtenberg (opening act)"; 1 reel tape (Oversize 17)
    1. Uncle Penn; 2. The Arab Bounce
  - Dr. Bluem: L8 Class, waer_048; 1 reel tape (Oversize 4)
  - Dr. Short lecture on fats and oils, and poultry, waer_151; 1 reel tape (Oversize 12)
  - Drugs Show #3 Public Forum, waer_193; 1 reel tape (Oversize 15)
  - Duke Jupiter @ Jab 3/24/79 Set 1, waer_207; 1 reel tape (Oversize 16)
  - Duke Jupiter @ Jab 3/24/79 Set 2 Part 1, waer_206; 1 reel tape (Oversize 16)
  - Duke Jupiter @ Jab 3/24/79 Set 2 Part 2, waer_208; 1 reel tape (Oversize 16)
  - Dylan, waer_205; 1 reel tape (Oversize 16)
  - Eastern Lights, waer_189; 1 reel tape (Oversize 15)
  - Ed Levine’s The Jock, waer_222; 1 reel tape (Oversize 16)
  - Edward Asner for the Great American Smokeout, waer_259; 1 reel tape (Oversize 18)
  - Ellen McIlwaine, waer_231; 1 reel tape (Oversize 17)
  - Eric Andersen, waer_141; 1 reel tape (Oversize 11)
    Hello Sun; Close the Door Lightly; Why Don’t You Love Me (Like You Used to Do); Lie With Me; Blue River (static); Something I Heard Love Called; Time Run Like a Freight Train; Thirsty Boots; Mama Tried; Florentine
  - Eric Kaz Heads Out, waer_168; 1 reel tape (Oversize 13)
  - Eskimo Realities, waer_234; 1 reel tape (Oversize 17)
  - Festival Fan Fare 1965, waer_045; 1 reel tape (Oversize 4)
  - Festival of Arts: Stravinsky Concert Part 2, waer_013; 1 reel tape (Oversize 1)
  - Festival of the Arts: Catulli Carmina Part 1, Special Events Department WAER Radio, waer_014; 1 reel tape (Oversize 2)
  - Festival of the Arts: Catulli Carmina Part 2, Special Events Department WAER Radio, waer_015; 1 reel tape (Oversize 2)
  - Festival of the Arts: Catulli Carmina Part 3, Special Events Department WAER Radio, waer_016; 1 reel tape (Oversize 2)
  - Festival of the Arts: Catulli Carmina Part 4, Special Events Department WAER Radio, waer_017; 1 reel tape (Oversize 2)
  - Festival of the Arts: David Suskind Lecture recorded from LIVE broadcast, waer_018; 1 reel tape (Oversize 2)
  - Festival of the Arts: Shakespearian anthology "The food of love" part 1, waer_010; 1 reel tape (Oversize 1)
  - Festival of the Arts: Shakespearian anthology "The food of love" part 2, waer_011; 1 reel tape (Oversize 1)
  - Festival of the Arts: Stravinsky concert Part 1, waer_012; last words on this tape: "...the man who is behind the Festival of Arts this year at Syracuse..."; also, there is no fanfare at the beginning; 1 reel tape (Oversize 1)
  - Focus Community Action, waer_050; 1 reel tape (Oversize 4)
  - Folk Concert Series sponsored by Syracuse Peace Council and Salt City Song Miners, waer_232; 1 reel tape (Oversize 17)
  - Footprints ‘65 (Lecture of the Week), Feb 24, 1965; waer_037; 1 reel tape (Oversize 3)
  - Footprints ‘65 Tape #1; Lecture on Academic Freedom in Amer. Univs., waer_038; 1 reel tape (Oversize 3)
  - Freddie Hubbard, waer_154; 1 reel tape (Oversize 12)
    1. Intrepid Fox; 2. Uncle Albert, Admiral Halsey; 3. Here’s That Rainy Day
  - French 201: Tape 12, Side 2, waer_223; Intermediate Conversational French/ Revised; 1 reel tape (Oversize 17)
  - French 201: Tape 3, Side 2, waer_224; 1 reel tape (Oversize 17)
  - Gap Mangione Live at Jab, Spring ‘77, waer_090; 1 reel tape (Oversize 7)
  - George Ade - First Take, waer_251; 1 reel tape (Oversize 18)
  - Gil Scott Heron, waer_062; 1 reel tape (Oversize 5)
  - Gilberto Gil @ Jab 4/30/79 Tape 1, waer_187; 1 reel tape (Oversize 15)
  - Gilberto Gil @ Jab 4/30/79 Tape 2, waer_188; 1 reel tape (Oversize 15)
  - Good Rats Live at the Brookside, waer_120; 1 reel tape (Oversize 10)
  - Gov. Ross Barnett (Footprints Address) Part 1, March 10, 1964; waer_035; 1 reel tape (Oversize 3)
  - Gov. Ross Barnett (Footprints Address) Part 2, March 10, 1964; waer_036; 1 reel tape (Oversize 3)
  - Great Society - Norton Long, waer_138; 1 reel tape (Oversize 11)
  - Harriman Lecture, waer_039; 1 reel tape (Oversize 3)
  - Head 3-2-75 Tin Can Tin, waer_169; 1 reel tape (Oversize 13)
  - Heading South at Market House Music Hall, Oswego, waer_114; 1 reel tape (Oversize 9)
    1. Over The Hill to the Poorhouse (Part of...); 2. You’re Sorry; 3. Long Black Veil; 4. Pig in the Pen; 5. Goodnight, Irene; 6. Follow the Leader; 7. House of the Rising Sun; 8. Send Me Papa’s Fiddle; 9. Dusty Miller; 1. Goin’ Honky-Tonkin’; 2. Dueling Banjos; 3. I Guess It Doesn’t Matter Anymore; 4. Grandfather’s Clock; 5. Panama Red; 6. Mr. Bojangles; 7. Roll In My Sweet Baby’s Arms; 8. Corinna
  - Heller Lec., 5/1/59; waer_041; 1 reel tape (Oversize 4)
  - Hendrick’s Chapel Christmas Concert, waer_042; 1 reel tape (Oversize 4)
  - Hendrick’s Chapel Special: John F. Kennedy Memorial Service, Special Events Department, waer_028; 1 reel tape (Oversize 3)
  - Herbie Hancock at Kimmel Hall 4/26/74, waer_067; 1 reel tape (Oversize 6)
    1. Watermelon man 2. Vein melter 3. Sly 4. Funk-a-Lee 5. Hornets 6. Chameleon
  - Howard Guckert, waer_209; 1 reel tape (Oversize 16)
  - Humphrey Osmond - Psychedelic Memoirs, waer_192; 1 reel tape (Oversize 15)
  - Injuns, or, We Can’t Hold Out Much Longer Sir, waer_215; ZBS Media, Inc. R.D. 1; Fort Edward, New York 12828; 1 reel tape (Oversize 16)
  - Intercontinental Classroom; Story of ISO, produced specifically for ABC, waer_043; 1 reel tape (Oversize 4)
  - Jab Concert - James/Chris/Vinty, waer_091; 1 reel tape (Oversize 7)
  - Jab concert; James and G.B.; Chris; Vinty, waer_072; 1 reel tape (Oversize 6)
  - Jack Bruce, waer_194; 1 reel tape (Oversize 15)
  - Jam Factory on the quad, May 21, 1972; waer_096; 1 reel tape (Oversize 8)
  - Jean Houston, waer_204; 1 reel tape (Oversize 16)
  - Jesse Colins Young 11/19/73 Master, waer_157; 1 reel tape (Oversize 13)
  - John Brown’s Body, waer_052; 1 reel tape (Oversize 4)
  - John Fahey live at Jabberwocky July 15, 1972, waer_075; 1 reel tape (Oversize 6)
    1. piece #12. piece #23. piece #34. piece #4
  - John Gardner Interview, waer_191; 1 reel tape (Oversize 15)
  - John Houseman - Theatre and the Arts, waer_198; 1 reel tape (Oversize 15)
  - Johnson, Opening, waer_241; 1 reel tape (Oversize 17)
  - Joseph Spense 11/9/72 Jabberwocky, waer_082; 1 reel tape (Oversize 7)
  - Keim J.E. Levine Interview, waer_063; 1 reel tape (Oversize 5)
  - Keim on Film, Film Forum, Syracuse University - Rod Steiger Interview, waer_000; 1 reel tape (Oversize 1)
  - Ken Kesey #2 Tiller Tales, waer_197; 1 reel tape (Oversize 15)
  - Larry Coryell and the 11th House Crouse College 3/13/74, waer_059; late show; 1 reel tape (Oversize 5)
    1. 2. The Funky Waltz 3. Lolitta 4. Untitled unaccompanied (keyboard solo) 5. Theme for a Dream 6. The Lover Girl 7. Joy Ride 8. Right-on-you-all
  - Last "Night Call", waer_073; 1 reel tape (Oversize 6)
  - Laurent Lecture, waer_040; 1 reel tape (Oversize 4)
  - Lecture of the Week (From Morse), waer_019; 1 reel tape (Oversize 2)
  - Lecture of the Week [unreadable], waer_020; 1 reel tape (Oversize 2)
  - Lecture of the Week: "White/ Dennison", waer_022; 1 reel tape (Oversize 2)
  - Lecture of the Week: Marvin Kalb, waer_021; 1 reel tape (Oversize 2)
  - Lecture: Teacher as ArtistSpeaker: Prof. Robert Inglhart, waer_135; 1 reel tape (Oversize 11)
  - Legend of the West, waer_126; 1 reel tape (Oversize 10)
  - Live at the Palemino - KLAC Radio, waer_129; 1 reel tape (Oversize 10)
    1. Honky Cat; 2. Never Finding Love; 3. Sally Goodin’; 4. Good Woman’s Love; 5. Uncle Pen; 6. Julius Finkbines Rag; 7. Down the Road; 8. Darle Hollow; 9. Teach Your Children; 10. Tell Me Why You’ve Been Gone So Long; 11. Black Mountain Rag; 12. Keep On Pushin’ - Swing Low; 13. You Can Pick Your Friends; 14. Bile et Cabbage Down; 15. Fallen Eagle; 16. Orange Blossom Special; 17. Listen to the Mockin’ Bird
  - Livin’ End 2-27-75, waer_171; 1 reel tape (Oversize 14)
  - Lkhz at Zero live at the Cellar Door Washington DC Sept 2/76, waer_163; 1 reel tape (Oversize 13)
  - Loggins and Messina, waer_104; 1 reel tape (Oversize 8)
    Trilogy; Holyday Hotel; Vahevella; Your Mama Don’t Dance; Nobody but You
  - Loose; Livin’ End; Sam and the Twisters Tape - 1, waer_160; 1 reel tape (Oversize 13)
  - Loose; Livin’ Ennd; Sam and the Twisters, waer_165; 1 reel tape (Oversize 13)
  - Mark Almond at Jabberwocky: Part 2, waer_086; 1 reel tape (Oversize 7)
    Once I Loved A Girl; Sunset; Sausalito Bay Suite; Ballad of A Man
  - Mark Almond at Jabberwocky: Part 3, waer_087; 1 reel tape (Oversize 7)
    Last Set - Saturday Night; The City; All Go Our Own Way
  - Mark-Almond at Jabberwocky 2/24/72 First Show, waer_084; 1 reel tape (Oversize 7)
    1. Once I loved a girl2. Improvisation for flute guitars and cello
  - Mark-Almond at Jabberwocky: Part 1, waer_085; 1 reel tape (Oversize 7)
  - Max 11/19/71 Jabberwocky, waer_058; 1 reel tape (Oversize 5)
  - McKendrie Spring #3, waer_233; 1 reel tape (Oversize 17)
  - Middle East Crisis, WAER; NCC II 215 University Place; Syracuse, NY 13210, waer_227; 1 reel tape (Oversize 17)
  - More Rose Live in Studio 3, NCII Feb 9, 1975 Reel One, waer_069; 1 reel tape (Oversize 6)
  - More Rose Live in Studio 3, NCII Feb 9, 1975 Reel Two, waer_068; 1 reel tape (Oversize 6)
  - Neil Young at the Boston Music Hall, waer_137; 1 reel tape (Oversize 11)
    On the Way Home; Tell Me Why; Old man; Journey Through the Past; Cowgirl in the Sand; Love in Mind; A Man Needs a Moud/ Heart of Gold; Don’t Let it Bring You Down; Sugar Mountain; Vancouver Rap; There’s A World; The Danger Done; Ohio; See the Sky About to Rain; Down by the River; Dance, Dance, Dance.
  - New Riders of the Purple Sage Women’s Gym, waer_148; 1 reel tape (Oversize 12)
    1. Working Man Blues; 2. Henry; 3. Unknown; 4. Down In The Boondocks; 5. Garden of Eden; 6. Hello Mary Lou; 7. My Lady and Me; 8. Somebody Robbed the Glendale Train (and made off with the gold); 9. All I Ever Wanted Was Your Loving; 10. Unknown; 11. Take a Load Off
  - Next of Kin, waer_057; 1 reel tape (Oversize 5)
  - Nils Lofgren, waer_162; 1 reel tape (Oversize 13)
  - No Place To Hide, waer_044; 1 reel tape (Oversize 4)
  - Office Workers, waer_190; 1 reel tape (Oversize 15)
  - Open End interview program with music from promotion of "Monkey Grip" Album, waer_249; 1 reel tape (Oversize 18)
  - Orleans - Salt City, waer_143; 1 reel tape (Oversize 11)
    1. Time Passes On; 2. You’ve Given Me Something; 3. Cold Spell; 4. Live One Heart; 5. Please Be There; 6. Firefly Lover; 7. H; 8. Let There Be Music; 9. Sweet Johanna; 10. What You Gain to Do About Another; 11. If the Rabbit had a Bun; 12. Tongue Tied; 13. You Really Got Me/ Duke of Earl/ She Loves You; 14. I Found the Love
  - Orleans, waer_119; 1 reel tape (Oversize 10)
    1. It All Comes Back Again; 2. When It’s Over - Let’s Have a Good Time; 3. Please Be There; 4. Ready or Not; 5. If; 6. Two Faced World; 7. Tongue Tied; 8. Stoned; 9. I’m A Bum; 10. Called My Job; 11. Learnin’ To Be What I Want To; 12. Don’t Take Advantage; 13. Breakdown
  - Orpheus, waer_155; 1 reel tape (Oversize 12)
    Big Green Pearl; Monkey Demon; It Gets Worse Every Time; I Wanna Be Your Lover; Nummerity; By The Way.
  - Paraquat, Lyrics Enclosed; Copyright 1978 by John Anderson, waer_229; 1 reel tape (Oversize 17)
  - Parish Blue: Part 1, waer_030; 1 reel tape (Oversize 3)
  - Parish Blue: Part 2, waer_031; 1 reel tape (Oversize 3)
  - Paul Goodman Guest Speaker; Footprints 65, waer_132; 1 reel tape (Oversize 11)
  - Paul Sibiel Salt City Playhouse, waer_079; 1 reel tape (Oversize 7)
  - Pete Townshend interview, waer_139; 1 reel tape (Oversize 11)
  - Peter Pazer Trial Lawyer, waer_230; 1 reel tape (Oversize 17)
  - Pickled Herring, waer_110; 1 reel tape (Oversize 9)
  - Pink Floyd concert Given for Net-TV, waer_128; 1 reel tape (Oversize 10)
    no intro, fade up at beginning; Atom Heart Mother; Don’t Wake Me; Grantchester Meadows; Under A Canopy of Blue; Careful With That Axe, Eugene
  - Poetry Anthology, waer_201; 1 reel tape (Oversize 15)
  - Proctor and Bergman, waer_134; 1 reel tape (Oversize 11)
  - PSA’s - May to September 1976, waer_213; 1 reel tape (Oversize 16)
    See paper inside
  - PSA’s November to January 1974, waer_214; WAER Spots, Novermber - December - January; Late/ Autumn Semester 1974; 1 reel tape (Oversize 16)
  - Public Forum University College Education, waer_238; 1 reel tape (Oversize 17)
  - Rachel Faro and John Simon 2nd Set Jabberwocky 8/31/73, waer_080; 1 reel tape (Oversize 7)
  - Ralph Ortiz - Piano Destruction, waer_202; 1 reel tape (Oversize 15)
  - Ray Frenchman, waer_235; speech by William Kunstler at Univer. of Cinn. regarding the Chicago Conspiracy trials; 1 reel tape (Oversize 17)
  - Ray Frenchman on the Quad, waer_077; 1 reel tape (Oversize 6)
  - Richard Nixon vs. United States and United States vs. Richard Nixon Part 1, waer_173; 1 reel tape (Oversize 14)
  - Richard Nixon vs. United States and United States vs. Richard Nixon Part 2, waer_174; 1 reel tape (Oversize 14)
  - Richard Nixon vs. United States and United States vs. Richard Nixon Part 3, waer_175; 1 reel tape (Oversize 14)
  - Rock and Roll, waer_112; 1 reel tape (Oversize 9)
    Rock and Roll; Me and My Friends; In My Life; Come and Go; Hearted Small Business
  - Rod Steiger interview with Keim, waer_094; 1 reel tape (Oversize 8)
  - Rosalie Sorrels, waer_216; ZBS Media, Inc. R.D. 1; Fort Edward, New York 12828; 1 reel tape (Oversize 16)
  - Ruth Stout, waer_220; 1 reel tape (Oversize 16)
  - S.U. Jazz Ensemble at Jab 12/4/75, waer_252; 1 reel tape (Oversize 18)